<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ocenyapek</string>
    <string name="opisvain">Welcome to the Halcyon Fold. Join with friends in a free-to-play, real-time PvP multiplayer online battle arena (MOBA). Dive into a variety of game modes; from quick Brawl matches to deep competitive Ranked games. Vainglory lets you choose from an ever-growing roster of 30+ heroes as you battle in real-time to destroy the enemy Vain crystal. In this MOBA, you’re rewarded for strategy and teamwork — not for spending the most money.

----------------------

"This is one of the best multiplayer experiences on mobile. Vainglory is a totally legit MOBA experience, available any time in the palm of your hand." —IGN

“Best Mobile Game” —2016 Global Mobile Awards

“Sets the bar in terms of visuals, balance and controls.” —TouchArcade

----------------------

Features:

== Casual, Ranked and Quickplay Modes ==
Vainglory offers real-time MOBA combat with and against bots or live players. Whether you’re ranking up with your guild or just want to hop into a five-minute play session, Vainglory has the gameplay style for you.

== 30+ Playable Heroes  Unlockable skins ==
Choose a hero that fits your playstyle. Carry your team with a high-damage hero, dominate the jungle or lead your team into battle as a Captain. Then collect three different tiers of skins (and the seasonal special edition skins) that fit your personality!

== Touch Controls  E.V.I.L Engine Designed for Mobile ==
Designed for mobile, Vainglory’s game engine is made for intense, battles with 60 FPS. No need for a joystick; Vainglory’s pinpoint touch controls offer sub-30ms control responsiveness. In simple terms, you tap on the enemy: They die.

== Guilds and Teams ==
Need someone to play with? Vainglory’s built-in Guild Finder makes finding a team at your skill level simple. Create a team to climb ranks as a group or play with your Guild to earn even more rewards.

== Chests and Rewards ==
Collect in-game currency to unlock amazing tiered rewards like skins, heroes and more! Find Mystery Keys to get bonuses and the opportunity to get huge payouts.

== Worldwide Competitive Esports ==
Vainglory has official competitive circuits in multiple regions around the world. Seasonal tournaments and live esports events are broadcast regularly.

== Vibrant Community ==
Vainglory is a global community in 17 different languages that thrives on the support of active players. Follow Vainglory’s official social media channels for the latest news and announcements!

----------------------

Twitter: https://twitter.com/vainglory
Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/vainglorygame/
Twitch: https://www.twitch.tv/vainglory
Reddit: https://www.reddit.com/r/vainglorygame
Official Vainglory Forums: http://forums.vainglorygame.com/</string>
    <string name="opisarena">Experience Arena of Valor, an epic new 5v5 multiplayer online battle arena (MOBA) designed by Tencent Games!

Master unique and powerful heroes while teaming up with friends. Create the most dominating team the MOBA world has ever seen!

Call on your teammates to join you in the jungle! Crush your enemies in classic 5v5 combat in real time! Draw first blood, carry your team, and become legendary in the arena!

Features:

- Classic 5v5 MOBA, Perfected for Mobile -
Traverse a classic three-lane arena filled with nooks and crannies between towers. Watch out for enemies lurking in the brush and uncover secrets that wait in the jungle. Intuitive controls specifically designed for mobile will have you racking up kills with ease and make you an MVP in no time!

- Growing Number of Legendary Heroes -
Explore and command a roster of over 40 fearless heroes and counting, including a variety of Tanks, Assassins, Mages, Support, Warriors, and Marksmen. Build the perfect team to crush your opponents in battle!

- The Ultimate MOBA Experience -
First Blood, Double Kill, Triple Kill… all the features that you know and love right at your fingertips. Discover and dominate all the gameplay modes, including 5v5, 3v3, 1v1, and a unique “Hook Wars” mode that will challenge your skills and make you a true champion!

- Fast Matchmaking  10-Minute Matches -
Team up with players all around the world in an instant. Carve your way through jungles, lanes, and towers, draw first blood and destroy the enemy Core. Carry your team to victory in less than 10 minutes!

- Join Your Friends in Fierce Team Battles -
Enjoy fast-paced combat and forge alliances with players around the world. Interact with friends and guild buddies every day using real-time voice chat. Share the load, work together, and fight strategically. Team up with your friends in Tourney Mode and soon you’ll be able to create your own league. Arena of Valor is the new eSport for your mobile devices.

- Got What It Takes? Free to Play Forever -
In Arena of Valor, it’s all about skill. We strive to create the most riveting and balanced gameplay, so you can turn the tide of battle and vie for glory no matter the odds. Win or lose, every action counts!

Contact Us:
Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/ArenaofValor
Youtube: https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCgYkGvtBuY4onYm2Eh61zwQ
Twitter: https://twitter.com/arenaofvalor
Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/arenaofvalor/</string>
</resources>
